Ow!
There's supposed to be a chair there.
It's the chair's fault you can't sit down(!)
Look what my aunt sent me.
Wicked!
Not exactly a healthy breakfast.
Where have all the cereals gone?
Oh, what?!
Look!
It's happened again.
Just like yesterday.
What...?
This is getting weird.
Maybe it's burglars.
They steal, not rearrange.
Maybe it's the type of... makeover burglars!
What about wolves?
Did you just say wolves?
OK, not wolves but...bears!
What about...ghosts?
Please!
Who do you think's moving the stuff about, Tracy?
Bears or ghosts?
Interesting question, Bouncer, but I don't have time to answer it.
Cam's got tickets to an exclusive screening of a Hollywood movie.
Big smile.
And tonight's premiere will star Tracy's mum!
Adele told me to tell you that Cam rang and she can't make it.
What?
Oh, yeah!
I'm not really that bothered.
I hate limos and tiaras and movie stars.
It's all so...phoney.
Yeah, course it is.
Why did you stand me up?
I'm sorry.
Me too.
What's going on?
Tracy, I'm ill.
My headache feels like a car alarm going off, my stomach won't stop... and I've got a temperature.
I feel awful.
Oh, right.
Oh, dear, Cam.
Well, it's lucky I've come round.
You'll get the full service.
Tracy, thanks, but I really need some rest.
I will see you when I'm better, OK.
Ben, I need blankets, medicines and home comforts.
We'll raid the Dumping Ground.
Of course Cam needs my help!
She just hasn't realised it.
She doesn't have faith in the skills of Dr Beaker.
What could be so important...?
Delivery for Miss Wilson!
Tracy, what...?
You need looking after.
I checked the internet and the medical dictionary.
You've either got an Amazonian stomach snake, or flu.
Just to be safe, I'm prescribing bed rest, a nice warm temperature, plenty of liquids, vitamin-filled meals and plenty of sleep and a chocolate bar you can use as a desk!
Tracy, I'm all right.
I don't need your help.
I just need quiet.
OK.
If you don't need my help, I'll go.
(She's delirious. )
Who's got it?
I don't care what the story is, I want it back NOW!
What?
The present from my aunt - my chocolate bar?
It's hard to lose, so who's got it?
Oh, I get it!
I get the blame for everything.
Has anyone noticed Tracy borrowing things?
She took my pillow and a plant.
Nothing.
She's probably taken it away to eat it all and get rid of the evidence.
Who's going to tell Jenny?
No-one.
Walking furniture... moving cereal...
There's more to this than chocolate theft.
I just need a chance to solve the mystery of...the Nightstalker.
"Nightstalker."
Yeah, I like it.
Count me in.
Nightstalker's gonna get stalked.
We'll all sleep safer in our beds tonight(!)
Hi, there.
I'm here to see the...person in charge.
You mean Mr Byron?
Delivery for My Byron.
Hello.
I've got the next children's bestseller here.
You can read it, but I advise you to just start the adverts now.
I'm a typical kid and I loved it.
It's just gone 0300 hours.
Perhaps we should go downstairs.
No.
Go to bed.
Shut up, Bounce!
The Nightstalker's not here.
CREAKING The Nightstalker!
The cricket bat!
YOU use it.
You asked for it!
To make sure you had it.
Yeah, but...
Aaaaargh!
Keep the noise down, boys.
The Nightstalker might hear you.
(Louise. )
(Hey, Lou!
Louise!)
What...what time is it?
5.15.
I heard creaking downstairs.
I think it's Tracy, up to her tricks again.
Come on!
Tracy's going to be so embarrassed once we catch her out!
Lol!
It was SO funny!
He was like the mummy!
Yeah, well...
I was just putting it on to fool you.
It worked a treat.
So, why did you let us put that necklace on you?
Yeah, you really... (!)
That was stupid.
You're not meant to do anything to wake a sleepwalker.
Right.
Ha!
"You need vitamin C."
"Thank you for submitting your manuscript, but it's not for us..."
It's a bargain price.
My foster mother's ill, but she's a writer, so we need something with more pizzazz.
Tracy!
Oh, hi, Cam.
Feeling better?
This is a rejection for my children's book.
Oh, I'm sorry...
For sale?!
Better luck next time.
The book I hadn't finished yet.
I have to do everything for you!
Tracy, don't push it.
My mum used to be this interfering and that's why I left home at 15.
At least I try to look after you!
Hey, I did try.
It just didn't work out, that's all.
OK.
Well, you're not my mum and I'm not yours, so leave it at that!
Anyone want clothes?
Tracy had a clear-out.
I've got some for my fashion project on the '80s.
You should see what Tracy took Cam - fruit and the biggest chocolate bar.
Did you just say "chocolate"?
I can't believe Tracy nicked it.
Can't trust anyone with that hair.
Guess what...?
Um, I was gonna tell you.
I found it in...
Tracy's room.
Yeah, right(!)
You...chocolate thief!
Hi, Cam.
Hello, Tracy.
I want to say, about the books, the clothes, the chocolates... actually, that was Ben, but everything else...
Yep?
I want to say I'm not sorry.
NOT sorry?
No.
I was trying to do my best for you.
I'll always do anything I can for you, so I'm not sorry.
Right.
Great(!)
Well, you were wrong and you tried to take over my life and got it all wrong, so...non-apology not accepted.
OK.
Good.
Now we haven't got that sorted, I've got some tickets to another press screening.
I could squeeze it into my schedule.
Excellent.
I've replenished my wardrobe from a charity shop, so I'll be wearing this.
Lol?
Bouncer!
Don't wake...the sleepwalker.
Dangerous to wake... the sleepwalker.
Nice try, but sleepwalkers don't get the highest score on Death Raid.
Louise, go on, a bit more!
That piece is tiny!
I know, but this way it'll last.
CRASHING What was that?
Let's go and see.
We'd better be quiet.
I know!
Quiet, Louise.
OW!
Justine, shut up!
Louise...
Justine...
Lol!
Let's get him!
I can't believe this has happened.
Where am I?
Why are you two so wet?
- Lol!
This is so weird.
I'm so sorry.
LOL!
How do you annoy an adult?
Watch and learn!
I was here first!
I bagsied it at breakfast!
I never heard you!
You were stuck under your duvet!
Anyone who starts fighting stays here!
I worked hard to get you on this day trip for deprived city kids.
Act more deprived and less cocky!
I'll see my first sheep!
It's Lara Croft!
Shut it, Justine!
Do we need the rope?
It pays to be prepared, my mum says.
Here we go.
My mum's explored the world.
She's taken me to places not on any map.
Leave the line, Tracy!
What if I need to rescue someone from quicksand?!
Fair point.
Sure you don't want to come?
You organised it.
Someone's got to hold down the fort.
I've got some paperwork to do so...
Are you ready, kids?
Bye, Jenny!
Bye!
Yes!
A whole day to myself and it was worth it!
Is this it?
GOAT BLEATS A field in the middle of nowhere.
Not exactly Alton Towers, is it?
Come on, let 'em know we're here!
Wey-hey!
Was it something you put in their cornflakes?
No.
They're just like spring lambs.
You must be the lot from Stowey House.
Ready for action?
Oh... !
I was thinking you'd all be boys.
Of course, girls get put in...
I mean anyone can end up in...
Yeah, well, hello to you, too.
Welcome.
This is Nathan.
Gordon Hagley.
Farmer, man and boy.
We provide new experiences for people who hardly ever get into the country.
And this is your field of dreams!
Let's start with the assault course.
Assault course?
Wicked!
Where are the animals?
My son Warren built it.
Don't you worry your pretty heads.
There's something for everyone.
There's an animal petting enclosure.
- WE can go on the assault course!
Yeah!
..
Is it very dirty?
- Oh, do me a favour!
You have to be fit!
You get out of breath watching football!
Us girls will beat you!
It's only built for two at a time.
Me and Louise will be on a team.
Adele and I will beat you!
Easy!
Wait...
I want to see the animals!
I'll get Warren to show you.
I'll just sort these two out.
Right!
Come on, on your feet!
Out here, we lead by example!
Now...
I'm timing you!
"..Leave a message and we'll get back to you.
Bye."
BEEP "It's Elaine.
Jenny, can you pick up, please?
"My battery's running low and I need to speak...
Kevin, put those down!
"Did you swallow one of those?
Put them down..."
Why should I suffer when they're off having fun?
"If you get this message, call me straight back."
Come on, find the inner you!
The inner me will be the outer me in a minute!
Ahhh!
LOUD RAP MUSIC Who taped over my Schubert?!
No way!
Count me out!
We're a team!
I'm not here to join the SAS!
I can't win on my own!
You'll find a way to level the playing field.
What?!
A way to beat them!
Pitiful!
You'll have no trouble beating that!
Even the girls!
Come on!
You can hold him.
Don't be shy.
Aw, he's so cute!
Isn't he?
This a private petting or can anyone join in?
This is Warren.
Hi.
He's showing me his rabbits.
Hey, rabbit Warren!
He's showing me loads of animals, but these are babies.
Where are the grown-up ones?
Ah, well, um...er...
You know what happens on a farm?
They milk cows and grow stuff!
Where do sausages and chicken nuggets come from?
Everyone knows that, silly!
A packet!
Dolly, they come from a farm like this.
Where's the rest of your lot?
Dying on the assault course!
I built it.
Did you?
I'm dying to try it out!
Yeah?
I'll take you round.
Cool.
Maybe you can show me the farm first.
Yeah.
You're free!
Don't worry, I'll rescue your friends.
Quick!
Before they make you into rabbit nuggets!
I'm timing this.
I'll send you off staggered.
First team...go!
Go on, Bouncer!
Go on, go on!
Not bad for city kids.
They'll never keep it up.
How do you know?
Cos I pegged the end of the tunnel down.
By heck!
Ahhhh!
I'm stuck!
Tracy!
Wanna start again?
No, we'll go later.
Right...next team, go!
Go on, Tracy!
Over the head, Tracy!
That's it!
Right, last team, go!
Go on!
THE GIRLS SCREAM Tracy Beaker!
- This'll sort out Tracy!
Good thinking!
Don't just stand there daydreaming!
Don't hang around, work as a team!
- Up and over!
That guy's a nutter!
Come on!
- Come on, Tracy's right behind us!
No, she's not!
- Come on!
I'll give you a leg up!
No way!
It's disgusting!
I'll give YOU a leg up.
No, I'll give YOU a leg up.
Thanks very much!
Tracy!
Louise!
I was only trying to keep my top clean.
There!
Now you haven't got anything to worry about!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Stowey House.
Oh, hello, Elaine.
Yeah, sorry, I was out earlier.
Today?
Well, I guess...
I am...
Hang on.
Lol, Bouncer is NOT a punchbag!
Sorry about this, Elaine.
Take those scissors off Dolly!
Tracy, put that fish back in the fish tank!
It's crazy around here.
Can I speak to you later?
OK.
Bye.
Day on my own - it's not too much to ask.
Not half bad.
They might just beat us.
Ohh, hello, Flopsy!
Aw!
Eh?!
The animals!
Here.
Warren!
WARREN!
What do you think you're doing?
Shut that gate now!
Dolly!
Hah!
That's the wrong way!
She doesn't stand a hope now!
The stock's over half this field!
Are you just plain stupid?!
I know what you do, nugget man!
Eh?
What do you know?
City kids don't know the half of it!
Leave her alone, you big bully!
I'm not scared of you!
I did it, all right?!
I let the animals out!
What are you gonna do about it?!
Dad, it's OK.
Just help me round them up, eh?
I'm not finished with YOU!
Thanks.
You were scary.
That's OK.
- Elaine!
What are you doing here?
I came to see if I could help.
- So kind.
- Don't mention it.
Professional women have to stick together.
The thing is, Nathan and Duke have taken the kids out.
To save me from losing my mind.
Oh, Jenny, you deserve a medal, you really do.
Yeah, well...
I'll see you later.
OK.
Bye.
I just thought!
Perfect!
I've got all these case notes to go through and there's no-one here to disturb us!
Wheeeeeeeeeeeeee!
Wahooooooo!
We did it!
We are the champions!
Oh, yeah!
I'm having a re-start.
I could beat your time with a bucket on my head!
Justine...wait for me!
GO!
Come on, Tracy!
THEY SHOUT ENCOURAGEMENT SHOUTS OF ENCOURAGEMENT Come on!
Now, I've got a bone to pick with you, little miss.
Um...
Hang on, now, be careful!
See ya!
CHEERING And we have a winner!
Yes, yes!
Ha ha ha ha-ha!
You've unleashed your potential!
- OI!
Sorry, you just need to chill out.
Thanks for the tour.
No problem.
Call me.
Ooooooooh!
OK, now, people, let's roll!
That wild cat, I want a word with her!
We provide new experiences for people who hardly ever leave the country!
Bye!
Subtitles by TFL Ltd BBC Broadcast - 2003 I'm Sam, her best friend.
I'm her best friend too - Toby.